- I just got here, and I think
I'm loosing signal already.
Hello? Can you hear me now?
(wind buffeting)
Sorry, sorry, I'll call you later.
Yeah, yeah, sorry.
(wind buffeting)
(phone clacking)
(lock clicking)
(door creaking)
(footsteps echoing)
(fabric rustling)
(Adele inhaling)
(soft piano music)
♪ Hello, it's me ♪
♪ I was wondering if
after all these years ♪
♪ You'd like to meet ♪
♪ To go over everything ♪
♪ They say that time's
supposed to heal ya ♪
♪ But I ain't done much healing ♪
♪ Hello, can you hear me ♪
♪ I'm in California dreaming
about who we used to be ♪
♪ When we were younger and free ♪
♪ I've forgotten how it felt ♪
♪ Before the world fell at our feet ♪
♪ There's such a difference between us ♪
♪ And a million miles ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ Hello, how are you ♪
♪ It's so typical of me to
talk about myself, I'm sorry ♪
♪ I hope that you're well ♪
♪ Did you ever make it out of that town ♪
♪ Where nothing ever happened ♪
♪ It's no secret that the both of us ♪
♪ Are running out of time ♪
♪ So hello from the other side ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ Outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ Outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
(somber music)